이전이야기 생략...
Previously
on "The Player"...
JOHNSON: Mr. Kane...
we gamble on crime.
My name is Mr. Johnson.
This is the House.
Cassandra is the Dealer,
and I am the Pit Boss.
Rain check. It's Ginny.
Say hi to the wife for me.
Ex-wife.
Nobody can see
your shame.
It's just a tattoo!
I don't like a life
without you in it.
[gun cocks]
GINNY: Alex!
No. No.
No.
Who brought her in?
Some FBI agent signed off
on the paperwork.
I'm your Player.
Welcome to the House.
We didn't think
we'd see you again.
Maybe I can find the person
responsible for Ginny.
And then?
They'll be sorry.
Whoever they are,
they'll be sorry.
??
??Go ahead now,
pledge allegiance ??
[engines revving]
??To the flag
[tires screeching]
??Ay-yi-yi
??Ay-yi, ay-yi
??Hey
[all groan, cough]
??Revolution
29 호송차가 공격받고 있다
999.
Unit 29 taking fire.
지원이 필요하다!
Need backup!
280번 고속도로에서
27번 고속도로쪽으로 지나는 지점이다
Passing Interstate 27
on Interstate 280.
지원이 필요히다
Need assistance.
놈이 차 지붕에 있다!
GUARD:
He's on the roof!
[tires screeching]
??Let's start in, in the city
놈이 진입하려고 한다!
당장 지원이 필요하다!
He's coming through!
We need that backup now!
[gunfire]
??Ay-yi, ay-yi-yi
??Ay-yi
??Ay-yi-yi
[sirens wailing]
??Ay-yi
??Ay-yi-yi, ay-yi
??I'm freakin' disillusioned
??This is a real revolution
[wailing stops]
??
카산드라
Cassandra,
새로운 게임을 할 시간이야
time for a new game.
??
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com
Kor sub: bravesfan
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com
영원히 계속되길...
Aww, forever and ever.
[laughs]
_
[cellphone beeps]
웹-에릭슨 연구소입니다
Webb-Erikson Labs.
이봐, 나야
부탁할께 있어서 전화했어
Hey, it's me.
I'm calling in that favor.
그럴줄 알았어, 친구
About time, man.
뭘 도와줄까?
What do you need?
DNA 테스트야
너 아직 검시관 사무실에 아는사람 있지?
DNA test. You still have your
contact in the M.E.'s Office?
당연하지
Of course.
[cellphone beeps]
희생자 이름은?
Vic's name?
버지니아 리
Virginia Lee.
알렉스, 정말 유감이야
Alex, I had no idea.
괜찮아. 너한테 비교할
샘플을 지금 보내줄께
It's okay. I'm getting you
a comparative sample now.
왜 DNA 테스트가 필요한거야?
Why do you need a DNA test?
그녀는 신원불명의 희생자가 아니잖아
Like, it's not like
she's a Jane Doe.
알아, 이봐
I know. Look,
부탁좀 들어줘
비공식적으로 테스트를 해봐
do me a favor
and run this one off-book.
누가 나를 감시하고 있을 수도 있거든
There's a good chance
I've got eyes on me.
??
[elevator bell dings]
날 어디로 데려가는거에요?
You want to tell me
where you're taking me?
우리가 모든걸 보여줬다고
생각하는건 아니죠?
You don't think we've shown you
everything, do you?
완전히 보여주고 있는거에요...
I'm giving you
the grand tour...
모든 접근 가능한 권한과
완전한 막후의 특권들을요
all-access pass,
full backstage privileges.
글쎄요, 그런 종류의 것들은 늘
Well, that sort of thing
usually ends in
알콜 중독이나
지독한 성병등으로 귀결되던데요
alcohol poisoning
and a nasty STD.
당신 꼬여있네요
You're in a cheeky mood.
금방 풀릴거에요
Trust me, it will pass.
케인씨
Ah. Mr. Kane.
기록실에 오신걸 환영해요
하우스의 중심 신경이죠
Welcome to the Book,
the nerve center of the House.
안으로 들어오세요
Please, come in.
이곳이 우리가 통계와
데이터를 처리하는 곳이죠
This is where we process
statistics and data.
에이다는 우리 시스템의 인공지능이에요
사랑스러운 여성이죠
Ada is our system A.I.
Lovely girl.
잠재적 활동을 판단하는데
항상 매우 유용했죠
Ever so useful in determining
potential activity.
범죄 활동을 말하는군요
You mean criminal activity.
도박판에 판돈이 걸렸어요...
There is a wager
on the table...
새로운 플레이어에 대한 새로운 베팅이죠
a new bet for the new Player.
이틀전, 샌프란시스코의
연방준비은행으로 향하던
Two days ago,
an armored security transport
무장호송차량이 공격당했어요
en route to the Federal Reserve
of San Francisco was attacked.
70만 달러의 화폐가 호송되고 있었죠
It was carrying $700,000
in U.S. currency.
지난달, 시애틀의 팩-얼라이드의
호송차량이 같은 놈들에게 공격당했죠
Last month, the same men hit
a Pac-Allied truck in Seattle.
다섯명이 사망했어요
Five dead.
일주일후, 유진에서 스털라 보안의
호송이 당했어요
A week later, a Stahler
security transport in Eugene.
7명의 사상자가 났죠
Seven fatalities.
그리고 나서 민간 경호차량이...
Then a private cruiser.
스톡턴 외곽에서 당했죠
9명이 죽었구요
Out of Stockton.
Nine dead.
모든 뉴스들이 이자들을 다뤘죠
These guys have been
all over the news.
미디어는 이자들을 카네지 크루라고
부르고 있어요
(유명했던 레슬링 팀)
The media has taken to
calling them the Carnage Crew...
마지막 강탈사건을 봤을때
잘 붙여진 별명이죠
a well-earned moniker,
considering this last theft
6백 십만달러를 훔쳤고
brings their earnings to
$6.1 million
사상자 수가 28명까지 달했으니까요
and their body count to 28.
이 자들을 찾고 싶습니까?
You would like to
find these men?
그렇죠, 하지만 저들은 그냥
대량 학살범들이잖아요
I would. But hell,
they're only mass murderers.
그냥 약이나 하면서,
도박이나 좀 하는건 어때요?
Why don't we make a twisted,
little game of it?
재밌을것 같지 않나요?
Doesn't that sound like fun?
케인씨
[scoffs] Mr. Kane,
뭔가 일이 있지 않는다는게
무슨 의미인지 아십니까?
you know what they say
about idle hands?
우리의 도박사들은
지구상에서 가장 부유한
Our gamblers comprise
some of the wealthiest people
사람들로 구성되어 있습니다
on the planet.
그들은 경제 전체를 지배하죠
They control
entire economies.
그들이 한가해지는건
세상이 원하지 않습니다
These are not the kind of hands
the world wants idle.
그래서 우리는 그들의 시선을
돌릴만한것을 제공하죠...
So we provide diversion...
games of chance
흥분되고 짜릿하고 즐길만한
도박이 기회를요
that excite and thrill
and entertain.
약이나 술에 쩌는것도 가능하겠지만
Twisted that it may be,
우리의 도박에서의 배당률은
극도로 작습니다
I assure you, the stakes in
our game are hardly little.
평범한 것들보다 어느정도
고위험이라는 말입니까?
So you're saying somewhat higher
than Go Fish?
에이다의 계산으로는 이자들이
Ada has calculated
the odds are 7 to 3
앞으로 8시간 이내에 새로운 목표를
공격할 확률이
that these men will strike
a new target
7대 3이라고 하는군요
within the next eight hours.
우리가 예측할 수 없는
변수들이 있긴 하지만...
There are a number of variables
we can't predict, however...
그들이 무엇을 목표로 하는지,
그들이 누구인지 등등요
what they're after,
who they are.
[computer beeping]
그들이 이곳으로 올거라고 확신하나요?
Are you certain
they're coming here?
그들이 이미 여기 있다고 확신해요
We're certain
they're already here.
베팅은 간단합니다
The bet is simple.
그들이 다시 공격을 하기 전에
당신이 이자들을 막을 수 있는가이지요
Can you stop these men
before they strike again?
당신의 딜러로써, 카산드라는
당신의 유일한 자산이에요
Cassandra, as your dealer,
is your sole asset.
카산드라를 이용하길 권합니다
I suggest you use her.
이자들은 흉폭하면서도 정교해요
These men are vicious,
exacting.
공격을 할때는, 난폭하게 공격하고
사람들은 죽지요
When they hit, they hit hard,
and people die.
그들이 여기있다면,
내가 놈들을 찾을겁니다
If they're here,
I'll find them.
그럼, 베팅이 시작됐군요
Well, then,
the bet is in play.
[computer beeping]
_
다수의 돈이 당신의
반대편에 걸렸군요, 알렉스
The good money seems to be
laying against you, Alex.
물론, 도박사들은 아직
당신을 잘 모릅니다
Of course, the gamblers
don't really know you yet.
당신의 능력을
그들에게 보여줄 시간이에요
Time to show them
what you got.
가서 놈들을 잡아요, 케인씨
Go fish, Mr. Kane.
??
통신기는 연결되어있어요
뭐가 필요해요?
CASSANDRA: Coms are online.
What do you need?
지난번 호송차량 강도사건에서 도난당한
ALEX: I need details about
the money stolen
돈에 관해 자세한 정보가 필요해요
from the last truck heist.
화폐 유통에서 제외된 돈들이고
Those were taken out
of circulation
연방준비은행에서 파쇄를 하기 위해
호송되고 있던 돈이에요
and on their way to the Federal
Reserve for shredding.
그말은 그들이 돈을 사용하기 전에
세탁을 해야할 필요가 있다는거죠
Which means they need to be
cleaned before they're spent.
내가 맞다면,
놈들이 라스베가스로 온것은
If I'm right,
it's no coincidence
우연이 아니에요
these guys came to Vegas.
카지노들은 돈세탁하기에
최고의 장소들이죠
Casinos are the best way
to wash dirty cash.
추적당하고 있는 지폐를 칩으로 바꾸고
You exchange the flagged bills
for chips
다시 칩을 추적할 수 없는
깨끗한 돈으로 바꾸는거죠
and then the chips for clean
money that no one can trace.
훌륭해요. 저한테 생각이 있어요
Nicely done.
I've got an idea.
카스, 뭐하는 거에요?
Cass,
what are you doing?
국가범죄정보센터 데이터베이스에 접속중이에요
Accessing
the NCIC database.
[scoffs]
당신 법무부에 해킹해서 들어가는거에요?
You're hacking into the
Criminal Justice Department?
바보같은 소리 말아요
나는 패스워드를 가지고 있다구요
Don't be silly.
I've got a password.
그 지폐들의 일련번호들을 알아내고 있어요
Pulling up the serial numbers
on the bills.
잠깐만. 카산드라, 당신의 카메라들이
지폐도 찾아낼 수 있어요?
Wait. Cassandra, your cameras
can find the cash?
카메라가 아니구요
Not cameras.
지폐계수기요
Counters.
모든 카지노의 현금보관소의
We've outfitted
every currency machine
모든 계수기들에
in every casino cage
극소형 무선 감시기를 달아놔서
with a wireless pinhole feed
직접 에이다에게 전송되게 만들어놨어요
that flows directly into Ada.
에이다는 도시의 어떠한 지폐도
식별할수 있다구요
She can identify any banknote
in the city.
[computer beeps]
찾았어요
Bingo.
3분 42초 전에
3 minutes and 42 seconds ago,
누군가 비토리아 호텔&카지노에서
표식이 된 돈을
somebody used the marked money
to purchase $10,000 in chips
1만달러어치 칩을 사는데 사용했어요
at the Vittoria
Hotel & Casino.
알았어요, 어딘지 알아요
Yeah, copy that.
I know the place.
[tires screech, engine revs]
[telephone rings in distance]
브라운 형사가 FBI의
레이크 미드 지부를 통해
We've been alerted
that Detective Brown
포레스터 요원과 또다시 연락하려고
is attempting to contact
Agent Forrester
시도했다는 경고를 받았어요
through the FBI's
Lake Mead Division, again.
전화를 바로 가로챘어요
The call was promptly
intercepted.
그를 이쪽으로 연결시킬까요?
Would you like me
to reroute him?
연결해줘
Put him through.
[tablet chimes]
[telephone rings]
브라운 형사님, 무엇을 도와드릴까요?
Detective Brown,
what can I do for you?
저는 에드리발리 수사건으로
지난 4일동안
I've been trying to follow up
with your office
그쪽 사무실에서 정보를
얻고자 노력했습니다
on the Edribali manhunt
for the last four days.
미안하지만 이제 연방 사건입니다
Well, I apologize.
It is a federal matter now.
그럴지도요, 하지만
버지니아 리의 사망사건은
Maybe so, but the death
of Virginia Lee
여전이 라스베가스 경찰이
수사중인 살인사건입니다
is still an active homicide
for LVPD.
그녀는 제 절친의 아내였어요
이 일을 그냥 손놓고 볼수는 없습니다
She was my best friend's wife.
I'm not letting this go.
그리고 제가 개인적으로 종결했으면
하는 사건이기도 합니다
And it's a case that I intend
to close, personally.
당신의 노력을 높이사지만
I admire your dedication,
제가 확언하건데, 저희가
모든것을 잘 처리하고 있습니다
but I assure you,
we got it all under control.
저를 어떻게 생각하시든지 상관없지만
Bigfoot me all you want,
협조를 해주신다면 시간을
엄청 절약하실수 있을겁니다
but you'd save yourself
a lot of time by cooperating.
제가 당신한테만 연락할 수
있다고 생각하지 마세요
You are not the only one
with connections.
주 검찰과 얘기해서
I could talk to
the State's Attorney,
당신의 사건 파일들에 대한
연방영장을 받을 수도 있구요
get a federal subpoena
for your case files,
어쩌면 당신의 직속상관에게
직접 접촉할 수도 있지만...
maybe even get a direct line
to your ASAC, but...
그러지 않을겁니다
I'd rather not.
잠..잠깐만요,
위협을 할 필요는 없지요
W-W-Well, now, now, now,
there's no need for threats.
형사님, 우리가 뭔가 확실한걸 찾게되면
Detective, as soon as
we get something concrete,
당신에게 알려드릴께요...개인적으로요
I'll let you know...
personally.
[click]
뭔가 문제가 있나요?
CASSANDRA:
Is something wrong?
우리가 다루지 못할건 없지
Nothing that we
can't handle.
계속 게임의 상황을 알려줘
Keep me apprised
of the game.
발생하는 모든 상황을 알고 싶어
I want to know everything
that happens.
그럴께요
Will do.
??
그들의 흔적은?
CASSANDRA:
Any sign of them?
카지노가 아주 붐벼요
ALEX:
Floor's pretty crowded.
그게 손님들을 검색하기 위해
Well, I can use
facial recognition
안면인식 프로그램을 사용해볼 수 있지만
to scan the clientele,
제가 보기에도, 당신이 옳아요
but from what I'm seeing,
you're right.
아주 큰 장소에
너무 많은 사람들이 있네요
That's a lot of bodies
in a very big room.
몇분이 걸릴수도 있어요,
어쩌면 더 걸릴지도요
This could take a few minutes,
possibly more.
신경쓰지 말아요,
내가 관찰하는게 낫겠어요
Yeah, don't bother. My eyes
can scan the room just fine.
[cheers and applause]
타지에서 온 사람들
Some out-of-towners.
이자들은 뭉쳐서 다니지 않을거에요
These guys wouldn't be
huddled together.
튀지 않으려고 할 것이고
They'd want to keep
a low profile,
붐비는 테이블에서 멀찍이 있을거에요
stay away from
the livelier tables.
강도사건의 신체 조건과 맞는
I've got someone who fits
사람을 발견했어요
the physical profile
from the robbery.
약 6피트 키에,
190파운드 정도의 체구군요
About 6 feet, 190, built.
1만달러 칩 더미가 테이블에
Got about 10 grand
in his chip stack
놓여져 있군요
on the table
in front of him.
확실한것 같군요
Sounds promising.
[computer beeping]
그를 알아요
I know him.
도미닉 맥콜이죠
전 특수부대요원이에요
Dominic McCall.
Ex-Special Forces.
그래요, 우리는 6년전에
뱅골에서 작전을 함께 수행했어요
Yeah. We worked an op
six years ago in Bingol,
내가 합동 특수 임무팀에 파견됐을때요
when I was loaned out
to the joint task force.
이건 우연이 아니에요
그의 생각이었군요
This isn't a coincidence.
It was his idea.
존슨이 이 게임을 골랐지요?
Johnson chose this game,
didn't he?
그래요, 핏 보스가 항상 골라요
Yes. The Pit Boss
always chooses.
나를 엿먹이고 있군요
He's messing with me.
그는 그의 도박꾼들을
즐겁게 하는걸 좋아하죠
He likes to amuse
his gamblers.
그는 확률을 흔들수 있는
훌륭한 자극제들을 제공해요
He's given them a nice twist
that shakes up the odds.
맥콜에 대해서 알려주세요
Catch me up on McCall.
그와 그의 부대는 2년전에
정부로부터 이탈했어요
He and his unit were disavowed
two years ago.
나이지리아에서 수십명의
민간인 사상자를 초래한
There was an incident
in Nigeria that resulted in
사건이 있었죠. 그 이후로 사라졌어요
a dozen civilian casualties.
Been off-grid since.
- 어떻게 할려구요?
- 가서 인사해야죠
- What are you gonna do?
- Say hello.
[scoffs]
잘못 걸었어, 친구
Bad beat, friend.
알렉스 케인
Alex Kane.
[both laugh]
어떻게 지냈어?
How are ya?
엄청 반가워, 친구
[laughs]
Damn, brother.
여기서 뭐하고 있는거야?
What the hell
are you doing here?
나 여기 라스베가스에서 일해
I work here, in Vegas.
그래? 무슨 일?
Yeah? What kind of work?
보안 컨설팅
Security consultation.
Hmm.
자네 이제 전역한거야?
You out of the service now?
그래, 명령 받다가 늙어버렸지, 친구
Yeah. Taking orders
gets old, brother.
자네도 알잖아
이봐, 자네도 나랑 같이 게임하자구
You know what that's like.
Hey, you play a hand with me.
술이나 한잔 하자구
Oh, let's have
a drink instead.
글쎄, 둘 다 하는건 어때?
Well, how about we do both?
이봐요, 아가씨,
버번 두잔 찐하게
Hey, sweetheart, uh,
two bourbons, neat.
나는 도박에 영 쑥맥이라
I'm not much of a gambler.
이봐, 장난해?
Come on. You kidding?
자네가 현장에서 일하던 방식말이야
The way you used to
run the field,
자네가 선택했던 그 카우보이 같은
you might as well have
been wearing spurs
작전의 움직임을 선택한 본능이 있잖아
- with all those cowboy moves you pulled.
- [laughs]
그때 자네는 큰 베팅을 하곤 했잖아
You used to bet big
back there.
보통 승리했어, 내가 기억하기로는
You usually won,
the way I remember it.
어쩌면 지금은 더 현명하게 행동하는걸지도
Maybe I play smarter now.
[slot machine dinging]
별일없어, 돔?
You all right, Dom?
사회로 돌아와 정착하는건
쉬운일이 아니잖아
It's not the easiest thing
to settle back in the world.
확실히 아니지
[laughs]
Definitely not.
여전히 그 모든...날카로운 신경과
I still got it all...
the jacked nerves,
낯선건에 대한 위혐을 감지하고 있지
the stranger danger.
때때로는, 아무 이유없이
아드레날린이 솟구쳐서
Sometimes, I wake up
in the middle of the night
한밤중에 끼어나기도 해
with my adrenaline pumping
for no reason.
그건 마치...
It feels like...
자네가 어디있는지 믿기지 않는거겠지
You can't trust
where you are.
약간은 작전을 그리워 하는 것처럼 말이야
Like you miss the action
a little bit.
어쩌면 아주 많이 그리워할지도
Maybe I miss it a lot.
Hmm.
고마워요, 아가씨
Thanks, honey.
고마워요
Thank you.
하지만 내가 여전히
가지고 있는게 뭔지 알아?
But you know what
I still got?
훈련으로 습득된
The discipline,
아주 날카롭게 벼려져서
that laser-sharp focus
항상 내 앞에 있는 것이
옳은것인지를 판단하는 능력이야
to see what's right in front
of me at all times.
자네도 여전히 집중력을
가지고 있지, 알렉스?
You still got that focus,
Alex?
우리의 자유와 죽은 동료들을 위하여
To our freedom
and our fallen.
우리의 자유와 죽은 동료들을 위하여
To our freedom
and our fallen.
[sighs]
조언 하나 하자면...
Piece of advice...
자네가 누구인가를 빨리 인정하고
the sooner you accept
who you are,
자네가 한 일을 빨리 인정하면
the sooner you accept
what you've done.
그렇게 하면, 인생은 다시 즐거워질거야
Once you do that,
life gets real fun again.
[chuckles]
판돈 올리고 한번 해봐
Ante up and you'll see.
오, 아니야
Oh, no, thanks.
아니야, 안돼지. 자네가 뱅골에서
날 위해 뭘 해줬는지 잊었을거라 생각해?
No, no. Do you think I forgot
what you did for me in Bingol?
자네한테 하나 빚졌잖아
I owe you one.
즐겨봐
Enjoy yourself.
몇 판 해봐
Play a few hands.
카산드라
ALEX: Cassandra.
알아요, 그를 추적할께요
Okay, I've got him.
그는 카지노의 북동쪽 복도로
He's moving towards
the northeast corridor
향하고 있어요
of the floor.
카지노를 나가서 왼쪽으로 돌았어요
Yeah, down the hall,
turn left.
[tablet beeps]
화물용 복도쪽으로 들어갔어요
He's gone into
a service corridor.
그를 포착했어요
Right.
I've got eyes on him.
건물을 나가고 있어요
He's leaving the building.
잠깐만요, 잠깐만
바깥쪽에는 감시 도구가 없어요
Hang on, hang on.
I don't have eyes outside.
감시 카메라가 없는 뒷쪽 골목이에요
I-I-it's just a back alley
with no cams.
위성으로 감시하려면
몇초간 시간이 필요해요
I need a few seconds to see if
I can set up a satellite.
몇초의 시간도 없다구
I don't have
a few seconds.
알렉스, 기다려요
맥콜이 당신을 사각지대로
Alex, wait.
McCall may well know
이끌기 위해서 간것일수도 있어요
this is leading you
into a blind spot.
확률적으로...
There's a good chance
it's a...
함정이겠지, 그래
Trap, yeah.
잘못 걸었다구, 친구
Bad beat, friend.
Oh!
그를 데려와
Bring him.
??
[chuckles]
[laughs]
지니!
Ginny!
[inhales deeply]
[gasping]
[groans]
자네가 나를 물고문하려고 한다면
You know, if you're
trying to waterboard me,
잘못 생각한거야
you're doing it all wrong.
[grunts]
나를 왜 미행한거야?
Why were you following me?
내가 자네한테 항상
매력을 느껴온거 알잖아
You know, I've always had
a bit of a man-crush on you.
Mnh!
자네는 이렇게 재밌게 굴지 않았었어
You know, you didn't
use to be this funny.
자네도 이렇게 미치광이는 아니었지
Well, you didn't
use to be a maniac.
나를 미치광이라고 하는거야?
You're calling me
a maniac?
뱅골에서
Back in Bingol,
나는 이 친구가 탄창 두개를
I watched this guy empty
two full mags
헤즈볼라 지휘관에게 쏟아붇는걸 봤지
into a Hezbollah lieutenant.
눈 하나 깜짝안하고
그놈 머리를 잘라냈어
Took his head clean off
without batting an eye.
[chuckles]
넌 아이들을 폭탄으로도 사용했었고
He was using children
as bombs.
그후에 우린 맥주 한잔을 했어, 기억해?
We had a beer afterwards.
Remember?
[static]
알렉스?
Alex?
알렉스, 내 말 들려요?
Alex, can you hear me?
[static]
[tablet whooshes]
알렉스, 내 말...
Alex, can you...
알렉스...내...
Alex... me...
젠장!
Damn it!
[elevator bell dings]
[cellphone ringing, beeps]
이봐, 무슨 상황이야?
Hey, boo.
What's the situation?
알렉스가 놈들에게 잡혔어요
CASSANDRA:
Alex has been captured.
그를 납치한 차량에 대한
단서를 얻었어요
I've got a lead on
his abductors' vehicle.
차량의 마지막 이동을
지금 추적하고 있어요
I'm just tracking
its last movements now.
이 게임은 내가 생각한것보다
빨리 끝날수도 있겠군
Ah. This game may be
shorter than I thought.
그는 당신이 그에게 허락한것보다
더 능력이 많은 사람이에요
He's more resourceful
than you give him credit for.
이봐, 나는 왜 자네가
이 특별한 플레이어에게
You know, I've been wondering
why you have so much faith
그렇게 믿음을 주는지 궁금했지
in this particular Player.
저는 왜 당신이 그렇게
못미더워 하는지 궁금하군요
I wonder why you have
so little.
[cellphone beeps]
[scoffs]
이봐, 그를 봐야겠네
Hi. I need to see him.
죄송합니다
Sorry, sir.
아니, 그를 봐야겠어
No, I need to see him.
손님들을 만나지 않으십니다...
He's not taking visitors...
Aah!
[groaning]
그를 정말로 만나야겠네, 괜찮지?
I really need to see him.
We good?
- 괜찮습니다
- 좋아
- We're good.
- Okay.
도움에 고맙네
Thank you for
your service.
네
Yeah.
[soft music plays]
장관님
Mr. Secretary.
잠깐만 비켜줘, 자기야
Give us a minute,
darling.
뭘 원하나?!
What do you want?!
제대로된 서비스로 시작하는군요
Well, some courtesy,
for starters.
장관님이 우리 도시에서
우리가 제공하는 친절한
I take it you've been enjoying
your stay in our city...
서비스들을 즐기면서 즐겁게
머물고 계신걸로 여기겠습니다
...as well the services
we've been so kind to provide.
"서비스들"이라고?
완곡하게 잘 돌려말하는군
"Services"?
That's a nice euphemism.
"성인용"이라는 말같은걸로 대신
Hmm. Would you prefer I use
a different term,
표현하는게 더 좋으십니까?
like "adultery" instead?
사모님은 그렇지 않으실것 같은데요
Hmm?
Mrs. Secretary would not.
장관님 집무실은 펜타곤에 있지만
Your office is in
the Pentagon,
영향력은 NSA 전체에 퍼져있죠
but your fingerprints
are all over the NSA.
이 자를 즉각적으로 제거하는
You will use your access to
sanction a black-bag operation
비공식 극비 임무를 승인하는데
장관님의 영향력을
authorizing a kill order
effective immediately
사용하셔야 할겁니다
for this man,
토마스 에드리발리를 죽이는데요
Tomas Edribali.
그럴 수 없을것 같군
I'm afraid I can't do it.
그럼, 뭘 걱정하셔야 할지 모를겁니다
Well, then,
you don't know what afraid is.
아니, 내 말은 에드리발리는
우리를 위해 일한다는거야
No, what I mean is Edribali
works for us.
그는 우리에게 활동하고 있는 테러 조직들에
대한 중요한 정보를 제공하고 있네
He provides us with prime intel
on active terror cells.
댓가로...
In exchange...
그가 국제 외교관들의 아들 딸들을
You allow him to freely
murder the sons and daughters
자유롭게 살해하도록 놔두는거군요
하지만 오늘로써 그건 끝났습니다
of international diplomats.
But that stops today.
그는 우리 자산이야
He's one of ours.
이제는 제 것입니다
And now he's mine.
자네는 자네가 이제 아주
달라졌다고 생각하는거야?
You think you're
so different now.
왜? 정착해서?
Why?
Because you settled down?
그래 자네에 관한
소식을 들었지, 알렉스 케인
Yeah. I heard about you,
Alex Kane.
본국으로 돌아가 결혼했다고
Guy got married
when he went stateside.
하지만 어떻게 됐지?
But how'd that take?
맞춰볼까?...그녀가 떠났지?
Let me guess...
she left you?
왜냐하면 결국 그녀는 자네가
어떤 인간인지 알게 됐다는데 걸지
I'll bet because eventually
she saw what you are.
아니
No.
아니, 그녀는 내가
누구인지를 일깨워줬지
No,
she reminded me who I am.
아니면 그녀는 자네가 잠시
망각하도록 만들어준거겠지
Or she made you
forget a while.
하지만 진실을 알아...
But I know the truth...
자네는 냉혈한 살인마야
you're a stone-cold killer,
나처럼 말이야
just like me.
내가 한 모든 일이 자랑스럽지는 않지만
I'm not proud
of everything I did,
그런 일을 초래하지 않은 사람을
피해입힌적은 없어
but I never hurt anyone
who didn't have it coming.
오, 뭐, 내가 초래한거라구?
Oh, what, you think
I have it coming?
넌 돈때문에 선량한 사람들을 죽였어
You kill innocent people
for money.
돈에 관한 문제가 아니야
It's not about the money.
우리가 원할때 우리가 원하는걸 하는거야
We do what we want
when we want.
얼마나 많은 사람들이
그렇게 살수 있겠어?
How many people
can say that?
더이상 규칙도 없고,
더이상 명령도 없고
No more rules,
no more orders,
우리를 죽으라고 보내놓고는
no more hypocrites on hills
sending us to die
우리가 죽지 않으면 불쾌해하는
높은 양반들도 없어
and then resenting us
when we don't.
우리 스스로를 제외하고는
누구에게도 복종하지 않아
We answer to nobody
but ourselves.
그리고, 친구, 요즘세상에는
그것만이 진정한 자유야
And that, my friend, is the only
true freedom these days.
그렇지
That's right.
자유...그걸 위해 우리가 싸웠지
Freedom... that thing
we were fighting for.
??
자네가 이해할꺼라 생각했어
I figured you'd understand.
알렉스, 내...말 들..?
내 말 들...?
Alex, can you he... me?
Can you... me?
카산드라, 내 말 들려?
[whispering] Cassandra,
can you hear me?
[computer beeping]
- 잡았어
- 물건이 움직입니다
- Gotcha.
- The goods are in play.
거래를 할거라면
If we're gonna do this,
10분안에 떠나야 합니다
we need to leave in
the next 10 minutes.
가자
Let's go.
카산드라, 내 말 들려?
[whispering]
Cassandra, can you hear me?
[computer beeping]
저 친구는 어떻게 할까요?
What about your buddy?
카산드라, 내 말 들려?
[whispering]
Cassandra, can you hear me?
죽여
Kill him.
뭔가 할꺼라면, 당장 해
If you're gonna do something,
do it now.
[beeping]
잠깐만요, 알렉스
Hang on, Alex.
당장 해. 어서, 당장
Do it now. Come on, do it.
어서 해! 어서
Do it! Come on, do it.
당장 해! 당장!
Do it! Do it now!!
[table chimes]
[generator humming,
slot machines dinging]
[coins clinking]
[grunting]
[gunfire]
[gun cocks]
그는 사라졌습니다
He's gone.
아마 경찰들을 부르러 갔을겁니다
He's probably gonna go
call the cops.
경찰들은...
The cops...
우리 상대도 안돼
그놈들은 허수아비야
are the least of our worries.
They're a joke.
우리 장물아비가 기다리고 있어
거래를 했다고
Our fence is lined up.
We made a deal.
우리가 전달하지 않으면,
우리는 죽은목숩이야
We don't deliver, we're dead.
일하러 가자
Let's go to work.
이봐, 도와줘서 고마워요
ALEX: Hey,
thanks for the assist.
맥콜의 부하들을 계속 감시중인가요?
Did you keep a visual
on McCall's crew?
당신이 죽지 않은걸 확인하게 위해
거기에 좀 열중하고 있었거든요
I was a bit preoccupied
with making sure you didn't die.
만약 플레이어가 죽으면
도박 확률에 별로 좋지 않거든요
Not really good for the odds
if the Player stops breathing.
몇 피트 앞에 새로운
하이브리드 차량이 있어요
Several feet ahead of you
is a brand-new hybrid.
제가 자동차 시스템을 원격으로
해킹해서 문을 열 수 있어요...
I can hack the car system
remotely and unlock it if...
고마워요
Yeah, thanks.
[sighs]
그치만 나는 고전적인걸 더 좋아해요
I like the classics more.
[engine revs]
[tires screeching]
옛날것만 좋아하기는...
A tad brutish.
맥콜의 계획이 무엇이든간에
곧 마무리될거에요
Whatever McCall's planning,
it's going down soon.
그의 목표가 무엇인지를 알아내야해요
We need to figure out
his target.
어디서든 벌어질 수 있어요
That could be anywhere.
알아요. 도시는 지금 피크 아워지요
I know.
The city's at peak hour.
거리들은 붐빌꺼에요
The streets are flooded.
만약 그가 지금 공격한다면,
피바다가 될거에요
If he hits now,
it will be a bloodbath.
[tires screeching]
[guns cocking]
??
아직 안됐습니까?
JOHNSON: Is it up yet?
우리 요원들이 에드리발리가
페쇼워에 있는걸 확인했네
Our men have Edribali's
location in Peshawar.
작전통제소로부터
실시간 영상을 보고있는거야
You're looking at a real-time
feed from tactical command.
토마스 에드리발리가 차 안에 있는것을
MAN #1: We can confirm
Tomas Edribali
확인했습니다
is inside the car.
승인을 당장 요청합니다
Requesting authorization now.
시행하게
Do it.
브라보 원, 승인을 받았다
Bravo One,
we have authorization.
알았다. 드론은 위치시켰다
MAN #2:
Copy that. Drone deployed.
목표 무력화 3초전, 2초전...
Tango neutralized in 3, 2...
만족하나?
Satisfied?
남은 여정을 즐겁게 보내십시오, 장관님
Enjoy the rest of your stay,
Mr. Secretary.
[tires screeching]
테이블 중 하나에서 무언가를 봤어요
I saw something
on one of the tables.
그건 로고 였어요
It was a logo.
파라몬드 시큐리티에 대해
알려줄게 있나요?
What can you tell me about
Faramond Securities?
그게, 독립된 계약 회사네요
Okay.
Independent-contracting firm.
나라 전체에서 귀중품들을 보관해요
They hold valuables
across the country,
대부분 은행들과 판매점들을 위해서요
mostly for banks
and retailers.
네바다주에 두건의 운송 스케쥴이 있는데
Two scheduled drop-offs
in Nevada,
그 중 하나가 라스베가스에요
one of them in Vegas.
뭐가 배달되는거죠?
What's being delivered?
2백만 달러 어치의
희귀 다이아몬드들이에요
2 million in
rare diamonds,
내일 개인 전시회에서 선보일 것들이죠
uh, to be shown at a private
exhibition tomorrow.
운전사가 지금 그 곳에 있을거에요
The driver should be
in the area now.
그의 로잭(자동차 도난 복구 시스템)을
찾아볼께요
I'll just pull up
his lojack.
카산드라, 트럭이 어딨어요?
Cassandra,
where is that truck?
번화가를 빠져나와서
다운타운쪽으로 가고 있어요
Turning off the strip,
headed towards downtown.
[engine revs]
[tires screeching]
[horns honking]
이봐, 당신한테 말하는거잖아
Hey, I'm talking to you.
[tires screeching]
뭐하는거야?
MAN:
What are we doing, man?
교차로에서 차 빼라구
Got to get that car
out of the intersection.
교차로를 통과해야 한다구
We got to get through.
- 차 빼라구
- 당신한테 좋은 밤이 아니군, 친구
- Go.
- This isn't your night, pal.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa!
[groans]
모두, 진입해
Everybody, move in.
[people screaming]
[tires screeching]
- 이동해! 이동해!
- 당장! 당장!
- Move it, move it!
- Now, now!
안으로 들어가!
Get inside!
[tires screeching]
준비됐음! 폭파!
Set! Go!
[gunfire]
날 엄호해줘
Give me some cover.
다이아몬드를 확보했다
I got the diamonds.
후퇴하라! 후퇴하라!
Fall back!
케인입니다! 제가 잡습니다!
It's Kane! I see him!
[groans]
밴으로 가! 엄호해줄께!
Get the van!
I got you covered!
어서, 가!
Go, go, go!
잠깐만! 놈이 안보인다!
Hang on!
I can't get a clear shot!
나 맞았어!
Aah! I'm hit!
[groaning]
한명이 당했습니다
We got a man down.
내버려둬 시간이 없어
MCCALL: Leave him.
There's no time.
[people screaming, gunfire]
계속 이동해, 이동해!
Keep moving,
keep moving!
[siren chirping]
길 비켜, 안그럼 죽을줄 알아!
Out of my way,
or you're dead!
이쪽으로!
- [screaming]
- Come here!
나와 함께 간다!
You're coming with me!
제발요! 안돼요!
Please! Please! Please! Please!
[whimpering]
[sobbing] Oh, God!
여자를 보내줘!
Drop the girl!
물러서, 아니면 여자를 죽일꺼야!
Back up or I'll kill her!
총 버려!
Drop the gun, man!
여자를 죽이게 만들지마!
Don't make me kill her!
무기를 버려
Drop the weapon.
비켜!
Get out of the way!
[tires screeching]
제길!
Damn it!
총 버려!
Drop the gun!
이봐, 빠져나갈 구멍이 없어, 친구
Hey, there's nowhere else
to go, buddy.
네 친구들은 전부 가버렸어
여기에는 아무도 안남았어
Your friends are gone.
There's nobody else here.
맹세하는데 여자를 죽일꺼야!
I swear to God
I'll kill her!
[sobbing]
무기를 버려
Drop the weapon.
내 말대로 해, 아니면 여자는 죽는다!
You're gonna do what I say
or she dies!
안돼요, 안돼!
No, no, no, no!
날 몰아가고 있어!
여자는 죽는다구!
You're stalling!
She's dead!
이봐!
Hey!
Aah!
[groans]
[sobbing]
그를 체포해, 체포해!
You take him,
take him!
알았어, 넌 체포됐다
You got it,
you got it.
[cellphone beeps]
카산드라, 맥콜을 놓쳤어
Cassandra, I lost McCall.
놓친 정도가 아니에요
You've lost more than that.
무슨 소리야?
What are you talking about?
그가 팔기로 한 물건과
Your thief is gone,
도둑이 사라졌으니
as well as the goods
he set out to procure,
도박이 끝났다는 의미에요, 케인씨
which means the bet is over,
Mr. Kane.
당신이 졌어요
You lose.
그는 어딨어?
Where is he?
존슨은 어딨어,
그리고 왜 당신과 연락이 안됐지?
Where is Johnson,
and why couldn't I reach you?
게임이 끝나면, 당신의 지원도 끝이에요
When the game ends,
so do your resources.
미안하지만 알렉스, 끝났어요
I'm sorry, Alex,
but it's over.
당신은 계속 게임이라고 하지만
실제로는 게임이 아니야
You keep calling it a game,
but it's not.
나에게는 게임이 아니라구
It's not a game to me.
이것들은 규칙이에요
There are rules.
규칙따위 엿먹으라그래, 카산드라
Oh, screw the rules,
Cassandra.
규칙따위는 상관하지도 않는
There's a highly motivated
killing machine out there
살인 기계가 밖에 돌아다닌다구
who could give a damn
about the rules.
만약 그가 그 어떤 규칙도 따르지
않는다면, 왜 내가 규칙을 따라야하지?
And if he's not playing
by any, then why should I?
왜냐면 당신은
그와 같은 사람이 아니니까요
Because you are
nothing like him.
나는 정확하게 그와 같은 사람이야
I am exactly like him.
유일한 차이점은 나는 행운이 있었던거고
The only difference
is I got lucky.
맥콜은 너무 나갔어
McCall's too far gone.
그의 내면에서 본 것은...
What I saw in him...
그가 빠져나오지 못한 곳에서
나는 빠져나왔다는어야
I was pulled out of a place
that he wasn't.
그는 멈추지 않을꺼야
He won't stop.
그는 그의 앞길에 있는 누구라도 죽일거고
He'll kill anyone
who gets in his way,
내가 그를 놔준다면, 그건 내 책임이야
and if I let him go,
that's on me.
??
말했듯이, 규칙들이 있다구요
Like I said,
there are rules.
하지만 당신에게 두번째 기회를 줄만한
But there's one rule
in particular
특별한 규칙이 있지요
that might give you
a second chance.
절대로 안돼
Absolutely not.
그녀가 무슨 소리를 하는거죠?
What is she talking about?
도박사들은 확실히 고무됐어요
The gamblers are
clearly invested.
당신도 인정해야해요
You have to admit,
꽤 오랫동안 오늘밤 같은 반응들을
we haven't seen action
in a game like tonight's
게임에서 본적이 없었잖아요
for quite some time.
카산드라, 무슨 규칙?
Cassandra, what rule?
새로운 거래죠, 두배로
New deal. Double down.
그는 망가졌어
The boy's a bust.
아주 나쁜 베팅이야
It's a bad bet.
이봐, 나는 당신이나 당신의 지원이
Hey,
I'm taking this guy out
있건 없건간에 그 자를 처치할거에요
with or without you
or your resources.
도박사들은 그를 지켜봣어요
The gamblers have seen him.
그들은 그가 무자비함을 할아요
They know he's relentless.
제 생각엔 하우스가 내기에
두배 혹은 0을 걸 의향이
I think they'd be thrilled
to learn the House is willing
있다는걸 알게된다면
도박사들이 짜릿해 할것 같은데요
to go double or nothing
on a wager if they are.
그런데, 그 내기라는건
A wager, by the way,
우리의 플레이어의 죽음을 건다는걸
확실히 해야 할거에요
that may very well ensure
our Player's own death.
그에게 어려운 목표를 주세요
Giving him the hard sell.
??
[computer beeping]
새로운 도박이 생겼습니다
We have a new game.
베팅은, 케인씨...
The bet, Mr. Kane...
당신이 오늘 밤 그들이
도시를 떠나기 전까지
can you stop McCall and his men
맥콜과 그의 부하들을
막을 수 있느냐 입니다
before they leave the city
tonight?
당신의 제한 시간은...한시간입니다
Your clock... one hour.
행운을 빕니다
Good luck.
이봐, 카산드라, 뭐 얻은거 있어요?
ALEX: Hey, Cassandra,
what do you got?
연방정부차원에서 모든곳에
도로 봉쇄를 했어요
There are federal road blocks
everywhere.
그 말은 도로 교통은 제외한다는거군
Which rules out
ground transport.
이 자들은 비행기를 이용할꺼야
하지만 일반 여객기는 아니겠지
These guys are flying,
but not commercially.
항공교통국에 접속할 수 있어요?
Do you have access
to the FAA?
내가 뭘 찾고 있겠어요?
What am I looking for?
라스베가스 지역을 떠나는
모든 비행 계획들을 확인했는데
Check into all flight plans
filed out of the Vegas area,
오늘 밤 떠나는것은
anything leaving tonight,
사설 활주로에서 떠나는
개인용 비행편들이 있어요
private planes from
private air strips.
앞으로 3시간 안에 6개의
비행 스케쥴을 확인했어요
I can see six flights scheduled
over the next three hours.
확률적으로는요?
Anything odd?
좋아요,
Okay,
이틀전에, C-130 화물비행기의 소유주가
two days ago, the owner
of a C-130 cargo craft
모하비에서 푸에르토 바하타로
항로를 등록했어요
logged a course from
the Mojave to Puerto Vallarta.
소유주의 이름은 아서 웨스트레이크에요
The owner's name
is Arthur Westlake.
뭐가 확률적으로 높다는거에요?
What's the odd part?
어제 아침에 총에 맞아 죽었어요
He was shot dead
yesterday morning,
맥콜과 그의 부하들이 도시에 도착했을때와
which lines up
almost precisely
거의 정확하게 일치하는 시간이에요
with when McCall and
his merry men arrived in town.
맥콜이 추적을 숨기기 위해
그를 이용하는거군요
McCall is using him
to cover his tracks.
비행기가 모하비에서 뜬다고 했지요?
Did you say the plane's
flying from the Mojave?
[computer beeping]
당신 위치에서 북쪽으로 15마일 위치에
오래된 비행기 폐선장이 있어요
An old aircraft boneyard
15 miles north of your position.
어디인지 알아요
I know where that is.
??
[tires screech]
[engines powering up]
다이아몬드를 확보했다
I got the diamonds.
좋아, 비행기를 띄우자고
All right, let's get
this thing in the air.
카산드라, 비행기를 발견했어요
Cassandra,
I found the plane.
출발하려고...
It's about to...
알아요. 서둘러요
I know. You need to run.
뭐요?
What?
당장
Now.
떠날 시간이야, 제군!
Time to move, soldier!
알겠습니다, 대장
Copy that, boss.
[engines whirring]
비행기의 원격 시스템에
침투할 수가 없어요
I can't get into
the plane's telemetry system,
하지만 공기역학시스템에는
접속할 수 있어요
but I can access the hydraulics.
당신이 올라탈 수 있을정도로
화물출입구를 열어둘게요
I'll open the tailgate just wide
enough for you to hop inside.
그렇게 할 수 있어요?
ALEX:
And you can do that?
날 못믿어요?
오, 그렇죠
Don't you trust me?
Oh, yeah, that's right.
날 못믿죠, 부끄러워하세요
You don't. Shame.
정말 빨리 뛰세요
You really need to run.
빨리요
Fast.
[groans]
Aah!
[both grunting]
[groaning]
자네는 그 칩들을 먹고 떨어졌어야지!
You should have taken
the chips!
난 자네가 그 칩들을 갖길 원했어
I wanted you to take
the chips.
자네는 뱅골일에 대해
이제 비긴걸로 하려고 하는거야?
You're trying to make us even
for Bingol?!
자네가 비긴걸로 하는걸
원하지도 않는다구!
I didn't need you
to make us even!
하지만 우리가 필요한 모든건
이 비행기 안에 있어!
But everything we need
is in this plane!
자네는 그냥 우리가 누구인지를
받아들이기만 하란 말이야
You just need to accept
that we are who we are,
그럼 세상에 그 무엇도 우리를
막을것이 없을거야!
and nothing in the world
is gonna bring us back!
그게 바로 자유야!
That's the freedom!
아니야, 돔. 난 그렇게 생각 안해
No, Dom.
I can't believe that.
그럼 유감이군, 친구
Then I'm sorry, brother.
[both grunting]
[alarm blaring]
꼼짝마!
Stay down!
자네에겐 기회가 있었어
You had your chance.
[both grunting]
??
자책하지마 친구
Don't blame yourself,
brother.
내가 널 잡고 있어!
I've got you!
안돼!
No!
??
고맙습니다
Thank you.
Hey.
- Hey.
- WOMAN: Hi.
이리와
Come here.
- [sniffling]
- Hey.
유감이에요
I'm sorry.
그녀는 떠났을지 몰라도
내가 항상 있어줄께
She may be gone,
but I'm always here for you.
무슨 일이니, 얘야?
What is it, sweetheart?
정말 유감이에요, 알렉스 삼촌
I'm just really sorry
for you, Uncle Alex.
뭐라도 필요하면 연락해, 알렉스
Reach out if you
need anything, Alex.
고마워
Thank you.
[engine turns over]
토마스 에드리발리가 파키스탄에서
Tomas Edribali
was found dead in Pakistan
약 4시간 전쯤에 죽은채 발견됐어
less than four hours ago.
그를 찾았어야 했어
I needed to find him.
그와 이야기를 했어야 했다고
I needed to talk to him.
자네가 원하던 종결이 아니겠지만
It's not the closure
you were looking for,
의미는 있는거야
but it's something.
자네한테 무슨일이 벌이지고
있는지 나에게 얘기해줄건가?
Are you gonna tell me what
the hell is going on with you?
나는 바보가 아니야, 친구
I'm not a fool, man.
라큅 가족의 납치나
The Raquib kidnapping,
어젯밤 번화가에서의 총격전이나
the shootout off
the strip last night,
양쪽 현장에 자네는 마법처럼
you magically appearing
and disappearing
나타났다가 사라졌어...
from both scenes...
자네는 뭔가에 연루되어 있어, 알렉스
you are mixed up
in something, Alex.
그게 뭔지 알아야겠어
I want to know what.
설명을 해줘
I want an explanation.
세상 모든것에대해
설명할 수 있는건 아니야
Not everything gets
an explanation.
경찰로써 묻는게 아니야
I wasn't asking as a cop.
그런거 알아
I know you weren't.
[sighs]
부탁하나만 하자...조심하게
Just do me a favor...
be careful.
난 여기 돌아와서 또 다른 친구를
묻고 싶지 않아
I don't want to come back here
to bury any more friends.
??
_
[sighs]
[chuckles]
[tapping]
??
안녕, 자기야
[chuckles]
Hey, babe.
이게 다 뭐야?
What's all this?!
쿵 파오 식당에서 파는
Well, it is only
the finest takeout
가장 근사한 포장음식이지
that Kung Pao Bistro
has to offer.
오늘 힘들었던거 알아
I know you had a long day.
자기가 제일 좋아하는걸로
깜짝 놀래줄려고 했지
I wanted to surprise you
with your favorite,
놀랐지?
so surprise.
[both sigh]
여기 얼마나 있을거야?
How long are you here for?
새로운 고객과 만나서 접대해야해서
I have to be in Arizona
in two days
애리조나에 이틀간 있어야 해
for a new client
meet-and-greet.
이틀이라고? 그게 다야?
Two days?
Is that all I get?
자기가 나를 더 빨리 만날수도 있었지
Mm-hmm. You could have
seen me sooner.
알아. 일이 바빠서
I know. Work.
그 직장 그만둬, 에이프럴
You got to quit that place,
April.
그럴 수 없다는거 알잖아
You know I can't do that.
그냥 광고 회사잖아
마피아도 아니고
It's a P.R. firm.
It's not the mafia.
혹시 그런거야?
Or is it?
내가 말해주면, 자기를 죽여야 할걸
If I told you,
I'd have to kill you.
하지만 더 좋은 생각이 있지
But I have a better idea.
??
정말 보고싶었어
I've really missed you.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
??
[door closes]
여기서 뭐하는 거에요?
What the hell are you
doing here?
도박사들은 당신을 꽤나
인상적으로 보더군요
The gamblers found you
quite impressive.
[scoffs]
당신은 고의로 그 베팅을 골랐죠...
You picked that bet
on purpose...
[scoffs]
내가 함께 싸웠던
putting me against McCall,
맥콜과 대항하게 만들었죠
the man I fought beside.
[clears throat]
당신은 내 머릿속을 장악하기 위해
나를 조종했죠
You manipulated me,
tried to get in my head.
나는 당신이 감정으로부터 스스로를
격리시킬수 있는가를 알아야 했어요
Well, I had to know if you could
divorce yourself from emotion.
이제 답을 얻었겠군요
Well, you got
your answer now.
내가 궁금한건,
여기서 진짜 뭐하러 온거에요?
You know, which makes me wonder,
what are you really doing here?
[chuckles]
당신 아내가 여전히
살아있다고 생각하나요?
Do you think your wife
is still alive?
지니에 대해서 무엇을 알죠?
What do you know about
Ginny?
당신이 옳다고 생각한다는거죠
Just that I think
you're right.
당신이 관련된건 알아요
당신이 벌인 일이라는걸!
I know you're involved.
I know it was you!
어떻게 했는지 당신과 함께 일하는
I know someone you work with
누군가가 그 테스트 결과들을
조작한걸 알아!
doctored those test results
somehow!
틀렸어요
You're wrong.
당신이 뭔가를 안다고 생각하지만
그렇지 않아요
You think you know what
you know, but you don't.
우리가 사는 세상은 회색과
그림자들의 세계죠
Our world is a world
of grays and shadows.
나는 당신이 누구인지 알아요, 알렉스
I know who you are, Alex.
당신이 무슨 일을 겪어왔는지 알아요
I know what you've
been through.
당신이 무슨 일을 했는지
무엇을 봤는지
I know what you've done,
what you've seen.
당신이 무엇을 잃었는지 알아요
I know what you've lost.
당신은 그림자들을 헤쳐나가는데 필요한
아주 훌륭한 장비들을 갖췄죠
You are remarkably well-equipped
to navigate the shadows.
왜냐하면 도박은 도박을
알아보는법이니까요
I know this because game
recognizes game.
나는...
I am...
아주 훌륭하게 갖춰졌지요
remarkably well-equipped.
하지만 회색과 그림자들은...
But grays and shadows...
내가 그곳에 다시 간다면,
나는 돌아오지 않을거에요
I go there again,
I will not come back.
당신 아내를 찾고 싶나요?
Do you want to find
your wife?
지니를 위해서는 무슨 일이라도 할거에요
I would do anything
for Ginny.
좋아요
Good.
그럼 내가 당신을 돕죠
Then let me help you.
??
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com
Kor sub: bravesfan